Everyone knows the head of House Flint is proud, mysterious
As distant and untouchable as a crimson moon hanging in the sky...
But...
Once you join Flint Workshop, you'll quickly discover that's not what milady is really like
I heard they're glued to each other 24/7...
I ship it!
Hey! Quit saying weird stuff over there!
Sorry. Porcelloy is in short supply, and your offer... isn't convincing enough
Th—This is!
Cuppa Moment's limited-time Maple Syrup Special... Times two
Hmph... You think I'd fall for the same trick twice...?!
As expected of Lady Claret!
Lady Claret! Lady Claret! Lady Claret!
Alright! That's enough!
Ugh, what a pain!
Oh no...
Roxy!
Seriously... Don't push yourself if your heart's not feeling well
It's been happening more and more lately... Hmph. What would you even do without me?
Forget everything you just saw!
Was that...?
Uh... some kind of trade secret, I guess...
Gimme that!
Huh?! Roxy! Give that back! You... Ahhhh Roxy!!
Should we... give them some privacy?
Nah... We're just getting to the good part
Huh?! Roxy! Give that back! You... Ahhhh Roxy!!